Owie! Where'd it go? Hold on.
These bones kind of look like
they belong to that thing.
This coin?
Could it be the incredible
treasure Hulemy was talking about?
I might as well take it then.
Oh crap.
Wait a minute.
Is this that stratum split thing?
Oh, this is bad.
Please, someone with the
blessing of might, save me!
I mean, you don't have to have a blessing.
I'll take anyone strong enough to
carry around a vending machine!
In my heart,
there's a lie in my heart, and the
sky is bright, and the sky is bright.
It's the time that the wind is passing
through, and the drama is moving.
I want you to die.
Everybody, everybody,
That's it.
Let me think here.
What should I do?
I'll turn into a balloon vending machine.
They could commonly be seen in
supermarkets and amusement parks.
Why is it so slow?
Come on, there's gotta be a
way to blow these up faster.
Wait a sec.
Maybe there's a stat I
can boost to speed it up?
Would you like to spend 10,000
points to increase your speed by 10?
Yeah, give it to me.
Oh, this didn't help me even a little bit.
In that case,
I'm a cardboard vending machine now.
Hand shaped from the finest cardboard,
these used to be popular
with grade school students.
What the hell is going on here?
Oh yeah!
Hulemy mentioned something
about this before.
She said there was an enormous labyrinth
underneath the Clear Flow Lake stratum.
It looks super complicated.
I'll take some pictures with my
security camera just in case.
That should do it.
I can put them together to
get an idea of the layout.
That was a 10 out of 10 landing.
But what do I do now?
Huh, that's the coin the
eight-legged crocodile dropped.
How am I supposed to pick it up?
Maybe I could use some points to
unlock a function that'll let me...
Wait, does that say a million?
Why do I have so many points?
That's right, I beat that big monster.
It makes sense.
Normally, you'd earn points
by defeating enemies.
Although I'd say I got lucky because
everything just kind of worked out I'm not
sure how good of a hunter I'd be so it's
probably best if I continue selling my
wares anyway what kind of stuff can I
unlock with my million
points I can feel it
this option resonates with my vending machine
obsessed soul yep I'm picking this one
Your vending machine rank
has increased to level two.
Ah, I see.
As long as it adheres to the basic
definition of a vending machine,
I can transform into a
whole bunch of new things.
Great!
Why don't we give it a spin?
I'm a coin-operated vacuum cleaner now.
The kind you'd see in a
self-service car wash.
It's time to suck.
I'm glad that worked out.
Now to find out exactly
what this coin does.
The eight-legged crocodile coin,
obtained from a stratum lord.
Wait, is that it?
Well, I might not have learned much,
but there's no harm in keeping it.
What's going on?
Your transformation time for today
is about to exceed two hours.
Please revert to your
original vending machine form.
Oh, I see.
I just need to turn back.
I had no idea there was a time limit.
Plus, I've got less
than 20,000 points left.
I better cool it with the transformations.
The weather is beautiful again today.
Not a single person has come by since
then, but that doesn't bother me at all.
Thanks to these babies.
I decided to unlock the
solar panel function.
So now I can save up points
whenever the sun's out.
And I don't even have to lift a finger.
All I have to do is bask in the sunshine.
This is the life.
Huh?
The heck is that?
They kind of look like little bears.
Or maybe cats.
Looks like they're being chased.
Just leave us alone, you big bullies!
Run away!
Don't worry about me, guys!
No way, we won't leave you behind!
One of them's injured!
Alright.
Here they come. Now!
Looks like that worked.
Thank goodness.
I hope those adorable bear
cats made it out safe.
Hold on, they stopped chasing us.
That's weird, they were hot on our tails.
There's no way they'd
just give up like that.
Where are they?
The little guys came back.
Where did this big Boxxo thing come from?
I don't think it was here when we
passed by this spot earlier. Who knows?
This is pure bliss.
I'd like nothing more than to sit here and
be surrounded by these Goddess all day.
But I have to figure out what's going on.
Hello there.
Thank you very much.
Pink and Pink!
Oh, crap.
I should have expected that.
If I lose these Bearcats now, who knows
how long it'll be till someone else comes.
In that case...
It looks different all of a sudden.
Be careful around it.
Hey, maybe we should just leave.
That kind of smells like meat.
Hello there.
Please insert coins.
There's a picture of meat on the box.
Maybe this thing sells food.
Yeah, well, I don't trust it.
This could be a trap using food as bait.
Pell, don't go near it.
Hey, stay strong, short resistant.
But it smells delicious.
Great.
I think I've figured out
everyone's names now.
The bearcat who's in charge is Mikenne.
The one with the droopy ears is Suco.
The chubby guy is called Pell.
And the darker-furred one is Short.
I just want to try one bite.
I'm so hungry, I can't think straight.
Come on, have some self-control, pal.
You're one of the pouched bearcat fiends,
a proud member of the Devouring Devils.
Devouring Devils, huh?
Wait a second.
I knew these guys
reminded me of something.
They're Tasmanian Devils.
As I recall, they're carnivores
that have quite the appetite.
Sorry, I can't take it anymore!
Wow, that was so tasty.
Then I'm going to eat one, too.
This must be where food comes
out if you feed it coins.
Don't fall for it, Suco short!
This tastes incredible.
I want to try one.
Mmm, it's so yummy.
Yay, time for seconds.
What would you have done if this
was all part of an elaborate trap?
Well, as the leader, I should at least
make sure none of it is poisoned.
Whoa, that meat's so
juicy, it's overflowing.
This has got to be the best thing
I've ever eaten in my entire life!
They never stood a chance.
Based on what little information I've
overheard, these bearcats are hunters?
and their group is called
the Voracious Devils.
But for some reason, their
expenses are incredibly high?
Which is why they've come to this stratum.
in hopes of earning a
bunch of money quickly.
Although, judging from
what I just saw them do,
I've got a feeling I know why
their overhead is so high.
All right, guys, now that
we've filled our bellies,
I think we should find our way
back to the maze's entrance.
Um, maybe we should back up and go home.
I mean, it's super scary here.
I'm just saying. Really?
But we haven't found any treasure yet.
Well, it's not like we're
going back empty-handed.
Oh, that's right.
That definitely counts.
While I don't mind being called a
treasure, I'm nobody's property.
Plus, I already have Lamas as my partner.
Too bad.
That scared the crap out of me.
I completely forgot this
weird box thing could speak.
You could even win a reward.
I see.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to serving you again.
It's almost like it was
reacting to our voices just now.
You sure it's not a coincidence?
Maybe, but the timing made
it sound like a response.
There's no way.
It can't think.
There's a distinct
possibility that it's sentient
and can understand
everything we're saying,
though.
Yes, I've been waiting for this moment.
Hello there.
Mm-hmm.
I guess that proves it
doesn't understand us.
It keeps on responding with nonsense.
That's not it at all.
Come on, think it through.
I can only say canned phrases,
and I have to make do with that.
Too bad.
You're right.
This thing only says stuff
whenever we talk first.
That's too bad.
I don't know why I expected more from it.
Oh, it's not that complicated.
Use your brains a bit more.
Even though this magic
item is dumb as rocks,
I say we should still
bring it back with us.
Yeah!
I give up.
At least they're taking
me to the entrance.
You should sit back since
you're injured, Suco.
Leave it to the three of
us to carry this thing.
I should have figured.
I could turn into cardboard
to make this easier,
but suddenly transforming
might scare them away.
Oh, I know!
Hold on, it feels so much lighter now.
Look, there are wheels on the
bottom of the box to help it move.
Whoa, you're right.
Were these here the whole time?
Heave, ho!
This is way easier. Oh, boy.
Now we can eat any time
we're hungry. No, wait.
This is a special magic item.
If we sell it to a place
like Chain's Restaurant,
I bet we could make a huge fortune.
Good idea.
Wow, sure, you're so smart.
Sorry to rain on your parade,
but I'm definitely not for sale.
Also, Chain's Restaurant?
I'd rather be in that
crocodile than with them.
We're getting close to the spot where
those huge hog fiends first showed up.
When they sprung out from
that fork without any warning,
I was so surprised I got hurt.
So that's what happened.
It might be best if I'd let
them know about my barrier.
What's this?
Looks like some kind of wall.
Are you guys okay?
It's too strong, we can't get out!
Help us, Beacon Ake! Suco! Let's go!
Is this your doing?
No, short!
Ow!
I had a feeling this
was too good to be true.
Shoot, I made them wary of me instead.
I'd better release Pell too
in order to clear this up.
Oh, it spit me out. Pell!
Why would the magic item
put us outside on purpose?
Hello there!
Look, it changed again!
Are you messing with us?
Enough with the hello there crap!
Oh,
I suppose I'll have to come up with some
other way of trying to
communicate with them.
Maybe I'll use that
function I saw earlier.
What the heck is that?
There's a whole bunch of funny
pictures moving in a line.
The only things I could put on
my board are my normal messages?
Maybe they're letters or something, but
I've never seen anything like them before.
Of course not.
Why would you know?
It's all in Japanese.
Based off everything
that's happened so far,
it seems obvious to me
that it's rejecting us.
Too bad.
Too bad, it says. See?
Just like I said.
You've got it all wrong!
This is so frustrating!
There's no way that
something that makes food
this delicious could ever
be a bad guy in my book.
I know, right?
I wish I could eat this every day.
Yeah, I totally agree.
I don't even remember why we were mad.
That's all it took?
You guys are easy.
That was the roar of a huge hog.
Let's get out of here.
There they are again.
This is a kerosene pump, often found
around gas stations for winter fuel.
Here we go.
Now to pull the lever and... Huh?
Right!
You have to free the nozzle
before anything will come out.
What a good safety feature.
Wait!
This isn't the time for that!
Ah! Now what?
I'm not sure what
happened, but I'll take it.
That's what you get, big dumb jerks!
Huh?
Something doesn't seem right.
What's that?
You're kidding me!
Oh no this is so bad!
The flame skeleton titan
Everyone run away!
Whoa, first a bunch of huge hogs
and then the Stratum Lord shows up?
I was so scared back there.
They say you get a sweet treasure if you
manage to defeat the Flameskeletitan.
But how can anyone take down
a huge monster like that?
I have to agree with Short.
That thing's probably unbeatable.
We're kind of in a bad spot right now.
But it soothes my heart to watch
them sleeping so peacefully.
I could sit here forever.
What's that?
I should probably wake everyone up.
Hello there!
Yeah, just give me another
20 pieces of meat, would you?
Me, Coin, sure.
That's not something you
should be doing in public.
Get a room, you two.
I'm getting a weird vibe
from Zuko's sleep talking.
Crap, they're getting closer.
I look forward to summoning you again.
Huh?
What's going on? So loud.
Those are flame skulls.
If we don't take them out, they'll
summon the Flame Skelet Titan.
Wait, what's their weakness again?
I totally forgot.
This bottle fell out
of the magic item box.
That'll come in handy.
Take this, you jerk!
Now's my chance!
Hooray!
We beat all of them!
They're surprisingly quick on their feet.
Maybe they're actually strong after all.
Not that you'd ever think that
from their usual demeanor.
Who knows if we'll be attacked again?
So let's each keep a bottle
of water at the ready.
Sounds good.
This magic item is pretty incredible.
When we were hungry, it gave
us a whole bunch of meat,
and then it gave us water
to put out the flame skulls?
almost as if it had a mind of its own.
Yes, pal!
You make a compelling argument.
It feels like we're on the brink
of coming to an understanding.
Hello there! No way! See?
All it does is say unrelated
random catchphrases.
Damn it!
Next time you're getting
cold fried chicken.
If I remember, we should be
getting close to the exit by now.
Hold on.
It sounds like there's fighting up ahead.
Yeah, I can definitely hear
the sounds of a battle.
I don't hear anything at all.
They've got some really sensitive ears.
It sounds like there's
a whole bunch of them.
Now what?
I can go and take a quick look.
Okay then.
Watch your back out there.
Sure thing.
Hey, come on over, guys!
Director Bear is here with
a group of adventurers.
We should meet up with them.
What's the director doing here?
I thought he was supposed to be
stationed on the Clear Flow Lake stratum.
If Director Bear is here, that
means I'm saved. Oh, yeah.
One of the hunters I saw was
incredible. She's strong.
Yeah.
She kept shouting, Boxxo!
But she crushed a bunch of rock fiends.
What are you talking about?
there's no way a human could
take on a rock fiend per hand.
I'm telling you, she did.
And I'm pretty sure she said something
like, I can't believe he disappeared again.
I won't feel better until I give him
a smack for making me so worried.
Why did the box suddenly get heavier?
Box, no! No!
Thanks, no!
There you are!
You know, you had us all worried sick.
Well, not me, of course.
I know that when it comes to
you, everything will be okay.
They really came down here to look for me.
I, for one, am glad to see
you're still in one piece.
It would have been bad
if we couldn't find you.
That was a close call, Shiro.
No kidding, Akka. Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you see, when we told Llamas
about how we had to leave you behind...
She was so angry, she caught
up in the captain's face.
Who knows what she would have
done if we hadn't found you.
That's right.
Well, everything's fine now. I see.
Lamas is the reason everyone
was in such a hurry.
Hey, long time no see, Director Bear.
Long time indeed.
The band of gluttons.
Not only did you find Boxo,
you even kept him safe.
Thanks so much.
Great work from the
Menagerie of Fools, too.
I owe you all a meal.
Hooray!
By the way, Director, what
exactly is this Boxo thing?
Ah, of course, you wouldn't
know him, Mikenne, eh?
Well, you see the magic item you've
been protecting is actually named Boxo,
and he's the beloved resident
of the Clearflow Lake Stratum.
Isn't this thing just a magic
item that spits out food?
I'm a little surprised you
guys haven't noticed it yet.
Boxo's an intelligent being
that can understand us.
Hello there. See?
All it says is basic
stuff like hello there.
The thing is, Boxo can only talk to
us by saying a handful of phrases.
Hello there means yes, and when
he says too bad, that means no.
Come on, there's no
way that could be true.
Look, was the stuff we
ate before fried meat?
Hello there.
What about this?
His name is short. Too bad.
Wait,
so are you telling me that you completely
understood everything we were saying?
Hello there.
Are you kidding me?
I look forward to serving you again.
I love the food for you.
I like itального했으면.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to serving you again.